<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yao-Chung Chen on Yao Page</title>
    <link>https://ferygood.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Yao-Chung Chen on Yao Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Yao-Chung Chen</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ferygood.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ML-Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://ferygood.github.io/notes/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ferygood.github.io/notes/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>Here are some useful links provided by Mia after mentoring club:
 Ted Talk, The best career path isn&amp;rsquo;t always a straight line Comments about Germany Cooperation, salary, Kununu Coursera ML course by Andrew Ng, link AWS Doc, good to study by oneself [link](AWS ramp up guide) Mia&amp;rsquo;s IThelp writings, find here  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Nextflow</title>
      <link>https://ferygood.github.io/blog/intro-to-nextflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ferygood.github.io/blog/intro-to-nextflow/</guid>
      <description>Currently learning Nextflow to wrap my workflow in a structural way. Here are some useful resources:
 Official website: https://www.nextflow.io/ nf-core: https://nf-co.re/ Learning documentation: https://training.seqera.io/  I also start writing my script in nexflow. You can find more detail in here on my github.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEKRABber</title>
      <link>https://ferygood.github.io/project/tekrabber/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ferygood.github.io/project/tekrabber/</guid>
      <description>Introduction     The name of TEKRABber comes from the idea that the largest group of transcription factors, Krüppel-associated box (KRAB) domain-containing zinc-finger play a role as a grabber of transposable elements (TEs). The aim of developing TEKRABber is to provide a user-friendly tool to estimate the correlations in selected orthologs and transposable elements between two selected species. It takes the advantage by using the orthology information to normalize expression counts, setting one species as a reference and the other as a compare one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of Git/GitHub/GitLab</title>
      <link>https://ferygood.github.io/talk/intro-to-git-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ferygood.github.io/talk/intro-to-git-github/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://ferygood.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 13:38:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ferygood.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>** Contact page don&amp;rsquo;t contain a body, just the front matter above. See form.html in the layouts folder.
Formspree requires a (free) account and new form to be set up. The link is made on the final published url in the field: Restrict to Domain. It is possible to register up to 2 emails free and you can select which one you want the forms to go to within Formspree in the Settings tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributors</title>
      <link>https://ferygood.github.io/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ferygood.github.io/contributors/</guid>
      <description>Thank you to all the folks who have contributed both technical and creative skills to this project:
   Desirée De Leon 🦒 (designed 5 of the custom color themes, made illustrations for the workshop, and provided general aesthetic feedback along the way)
   Garrick Aden-Buie 🧙‍♀️ (debugged headroom.js and lent his panelset.js code to the theme)
   Allison Horst 🐕 (awesome illustrations of campfires, seedlings, and evergreens, as well as my R Markdown hedgehog mascot 🦔)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://ferygood.github.io/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ferygood.github.io/license/</guid>
      <description>My blog posts are released under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
