<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Project Portfolio To Grow on Yao Page</title>
    <link>https://ferygood.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in A Project Portfolio To Grow on Yao Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Yao-Chung Chen</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ferygood.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TEKRABber</title>
      <link>https://ferygood.github.io/project/tekrabber/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ferygood.github.io/project/tekrabber/</guid>
      <description>Introduction     The name of TEKRABber comes from the idea that the largest group of transcription factors, Krüppel-associated box (KRAB) domain-containing zinc-finger play a role as a grabber of transposable elements (TEs). The aim of developing TEKRABber is to provide a user-friendly tool to estimate the correlations in selected orthologs and transposable elements between two selected species. It takes the advantage by using the orthology information to normalize expression counts, setting one species as a reference and the other as a compare one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tachyons for Style</title>
      <link>https://ferygood.github.io/project/giraffes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ferygood.github.io/project/giraffes/</guid>
      <description>Tachyons is a design system that allows you to design gorgeous interfaces in the browser with little effort.      Because Speed     Building this static site generator theme was the first time I used an Atomic (or Functional) CSS system like Tachyons. It&amp;rsquo;s a design system that provides very small (which means fast) CSS modules that you can use in your HTML. So, rather than writing every line of CSS, you apply the style you need as you write your HTML with easy to understand shorthand class names.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Palmer Penguins</title>
      <link>https://ferygood.github.io/project/penguins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ferygood.github.io/project/penguins/</guid>
      <description>“Grid is the very first CSS module created specifically to solve the layout problems we&amp;rsquo;ve all been hacking our way around for as long as we&amp;rsquo;ve been making websites.”     — Chris House, A Complete Guide to CSS Grid Layout 1
 Since I began building websites in Y2K, I&amp;rsquo;ve lost count how many times the phrase &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;there&amp;rsquo;s got to be a better way to do this&amp;rdquo; has passed my lips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bakeoff</title>
      <link>https://ferygood.github.io/project/bakeoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ferygood.github.io/project/bakeoff/</guid>
      <description>Formspree makes it easy to receive submissions from HTML forms on your static website.      Functional Form     This theme has a form-to-email feature built in, thanks to the simple Formspree integration. All you need to activate the form is a valid recipient email address saved in the front matter of the form (/content/forms/contact.md). Of course, the example shown below (your@email.here) must not be used.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
